<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kiddo</string>
    <string name="textFieldFont">sans-serif-smallcaps</string>
    <string name="headerFont">sans-serif-smallcaps</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="normalTextFont">sans-serif-smallcaps</string>

    <!--Choose daycare/school drop menu-->
    <string name="school_prompt">Choose your daycare or school</string>
    <string-array name="school_arrays">
        <item>DayCare 1</item>
        <item>Daycare 2</item>
        <item>Daycare 3</item>
        <item>School 1</item>
        <item>School 2</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Terms and Conditions-->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before
        using the Kiddo android application.\n\n

        Your access to and use of Kiddo is conditioned on your acceptance of these Terms. These
        Terms apply to all visitors, users, and others who access or use our service.\n\n

        By accessing or using Kiddo, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any
        part of the terms then you may not access the service.\n\n\n

        Terms and Conditions of use:\n\n

        You agree to be responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and other
        account identifiers and all activities that occur under your account.\n\n\n

        By registering to our application, you agree that:\n\n

        The full name, class names and teacher names of your child or children, and your own name
        will be provided to our service. We will not use any of this information other than to
        serve the functionality of our application. This information will not be provided to any
        third parties outside of our application.\n\n

        The name(s) of a child and children that you input into this application are indeed the
        name(s) of your own children that attend the daycare or school that you have stated.\n\n\n

        Termination:\n\n

        We may terminate or suspend access to our service without prior notice or liability, for
        any reason whatsoever, including but without limitation if you breach the Terms.\n

        All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should surive termination shall survive
        termination. \n\n</string>

    <!--Registration confirmation screen text-->
    <string name="confirmation1">Here are your login details:</string>
    <string name="confirmation_login">Email: johnsmith@email.com\nPassword: Abcd1234</string>
    <string name="change_password">(You will have the option to change your password at any time
        when using this application</string>
    <string name="confirmation_info">Your information:\nFirst name: John\nLast name: Smith</string>
    <string name="confirmation_done">Your registration is now complete. Click the "done" button
        to login and begin using the app.</string>

    <string name="add_child_prompt">Please enter the name of your child exactly as it is registered
        in your daycare/school records:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_parent_tab1">ParentTab1Activity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_teacher_details">AdminTeacherDetails</string>

    <!--Choose month drop menu-->
    <string name="month_prompt">Choose month</string>
    <string-array name="month_arrays">
        <item>January 2016</item>
        <item>February 2016</item>
        <item>March 2016</item>
        <item>April 2016</item>
        <item>May 2016</item>
        <item>June 2016</item>
        <item>July 2016</item>
        <item>August 2016</item>
        <item>September 2016</item>
        <item>October 2016</item>
        <item>November 2016</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_manage_classes">AdminManageClasses</string>

    <string name="anouncement_details">Full Announcement:\n
        Permission slips are due tomorrow for the class trip to see Matilda. \n
        Just a reminder of the details for the trip - the showing of Matilda will be at 1:00PM
        on November 23rd at Xxxxx Theatre.\n\n

        Date posted: Sat Nov 12\n
        Time posted: 2:13 PM</string>

    <string name="event_details">Science Fair\n\n
        Fri December 9 11:00AM\n\n
        Location: Main Playground\n\n
        Children will be showing off the science projects that have been
        working on, and there will be an opportunity for children to look at each other\'s projects.</string>
</resources>
